Gon Bogner

Computer Science and Entrepreneurship Student

E-mail <u>Gon@bgnr.net</u>

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/gon-bogner

Cellular 054-7606046

Address 39 Even Sapir st., Tel Aviv

Date Of Birth Nov. 6, 1998

Profile

Practical Electronics and Computers Engineer, graduate of Unit 8200. Has 3 years of experience in the maintenance of communication and RF systems.

Has experience working in a technological-operational team that deals with a variety of areas, including projects that deal with writing code of technological solutions, the ability to work under pressure and multiple tasks at the same time, high work ethic and a desire to succeed.

Employment Experience

2018-2021 Military service

Laboratory technician in the technology team in Unit 8200 .

The team specializes in testing RF sensors and electronic cards in addition to their routine maintenance that includes diagnosing and repairing faults and checking transmission and reception paths in cards.

Working with advanced test equipment such as :

- Spectrum Analayzer
- Noise Figure Analyzer
- Sional Generator
- Fluke
- Probe

Extensive control and knowledge of Xilinx Alpha Data cards such as:

- Virtex5
- Virtex6
- Virtex7

And working with the RF cards that accompany these cards and supplying it to the entire unit in accordance with the intelligence requirements.

Writing a GUI in C# to control appropriate intelligence components and testing equipment as part of projects during military service

2018 Planning and execution of a final project for the degree in Electronic Practical Engineer

Winning in the first place in The Innovation and Entrepreneurship completion - a national project competition

The project dealt with the subject of a smart parking system based on vehicle number identification and included:

- Planning and physical assembly of the project hardware, which includes soldering and connecting various electrical circuits
- Working and programming with Raspberry Pi 3 using a Linux operating system.
- Write custom code in C / C ++ using the Open CV library.

2018-2021 Chilies Events Produces and markets parties for ages 16-24

Practical Skills

- Programing Languages
 C,C++,C#, VHDL, Python, Assembly
- Familiarity with protocols GPIB,Rs232,SPI.
- · Work with advanced testing equipment
- · Basic knowledge in Rf
- Working and collaborating with external companies alongside engineers in research and development teams.
- Microsoft Office

Education & Hobbies

2021-Today

Computer Science and Entrepreneurship Student at Reichmann University

2019 Payton Course

In the Army academy

2016-2018 Ort Hermlin College

Diploma in Practical electronics as part of the Merom Technological Program of the IDF Intelligence Corps -Pre-Military Studies (**Graduation with honors**).

2011-2016 Irani Yad Daled High School, TA בגרות מלאה מגעי המחשב ותקשורת

2010-Today Basketball Player

In professional leagues

Scholarship

- 'Monday' Scholarship
- Reichmann University Honors' Scholarship